Where will you be when the end begins?
Diary of the Dead is a horror, fantasy, science
fiction film directed by George A. Romero.
A group of young filmmakers encounter real zombies
while filming a horror movie of their own.
Debra Moynihan, played by Michelle Morgan.
Jason Creed, played by Joshua Close.
Tony Ravello, played by Shawn Roberts.
Tracy Thurman, played by Amy Lalonde.
Eliot Stone, played by Joe Dinicol.
Andrew Maxwell, played by Scott Wentworth.
Diary of the Dead (promoted as George A.
Romero's Diary of the Dead) is a 2007 found footage
horror film written and directed by George A.
Although independently produced, it was distributed theatrically by The Weinstein Company and was released in
cinemas on February 15, 2008 and on DVD by Dimension Extreme and Genius Products on May 20, 2008.
Diary of the Dead is the fifth installment in Romero's Night of the Living Dead
series of zombie films, taking place at the start of the outbreak.
The film explores themes of zombie, struggle for survival,
found footage, horror filmmaking, college friends.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.